it takes one second for life to stand
still
for questions to start building up
for hope to turn into despair
for choices to be altered for life
itself to never be the same
just one second is all it takes for life
to take a critical turn
that is why we decided to stand by our
customers
and ensure their protection even in the
toughest of times
with a protection that doesn't stop in
critical times
presenting icici lombard criticism plus
a plan that gives our customers extra
protection without compromises
which offers them coverage for 92
critical illnesses
106 surgical procedures
multi-claim option along with optional
coverages for personal accident cancer
restore
so
get ready to make a new promise of
protection to our customers
and enable them to lead a worry-free
life
one plan that provides protection that
doesn't stop
[Music]
you